Onesmus Kathurima Kirimi

✓ onesmuskirimi64@gmail.com

+254768444502

Thika, Kenya

Kenya

Male

in onesmus kirimi

★ onesmuskirimi.netlify.app



Profile

A dedicated, passionate, and enthusiastic IT professional, knowledgeable in Networking and Frontend Development with 1 year of progressive experience. Currently seeking to learn and improve my skills. I'm a limitless learner always on the lookout for technology concepts to stay up to date with the dynamic IT industry.

Professional Experience

2022/08 - 2022/12

Thika, Kenya

IT Support Intern

Gretsa University ♂

- Troubleshooting and maintaining the internal networks.
- Diagnosing and troubleshooting hardware and software-related issues.
- Developing user manuals for the staff.
- Setting up electronic devices for meetings.
- Data entry on institutional ERP.

2019/12 - 2020/03

Intern

Juja, Kenya

Uzima Health

Education

2019/05 - 2022/12

Bachelor of science in computer science

Thika, Kenya

Gretsa University 🛮

Graduated from Gretsa University with second-class honors (upper division)

2015/01 - 2018/11

High school diploma

Chuka, Kenya

Ikawa High School

Graduated from Ikawa high school with a mean grade of C+

Skills

Network infrastructure and

troubleshooting

• • • •

Front-end Website Development

• • • •

HTML, CSS, Java-Script, Tailwind CSS and React Js

Database design and Management

SQL

● ● ● ● Mobile Development Design

React Native

iopinent Desig

• • • •

Backend Development

Node Js, Express, and PHP

 \bullet

Languages

• Swahili

• English

Interests

Hiking

• Learning new technological concepts

References

Brian Otieno Oganga, *Head ICT Office*, Gretsa University botieno@gretsauniversity.ac.ke, +254716705170

Peter Siele, *Lecturer*, Gretsa University petersielek@gmail.com, +254711707689

Kadenge Waa Yaa, *Tech Lead, Event Based Surveillance,*, WSU Global Health +254707240021, kadengeyaa@gmail.com